Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Television Projects
    - WAY BACK IN 1960 - Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller (Box 132, Folder 6)
      Air date: March 10, 1960. Celebrating Gamble Store's 100th anniversary (65 years early). Rev. draft, 01/25/60, 45 p. - Rev. draft, 01/11/60, annotated, 70 p. - Draft, 1/4/60.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Correspondence and congratulatory cards regarding Emmy nomination, 5/97 - 12/97. approx. 20 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised, 1/6/97, 124p. - Staff and crew list, 12/17/96, 10p.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised, 1/6/97, 128p (2). - List of different drafts of script (3 items).
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Invitations to private screening, 3 items. - Correspondence regarding screening, 4/97 - 5/97, 3 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Correspondence regarding network standards, 3/97 - 5/97, 5 items..
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Clippings and photocopies of clippings, 5/97. Approx. 70 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Post schedule, 3/21/97, 3p. Combined continuity and spotting script, 8p. Script pages, 3/97, 4p. Guest list, premiere screening, 5/6/97, 11p. Correspondence and photocopies of clippings, 4/97 - 5/97. Approx. 30 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Congratulatory cards and letters, 5/97. 28 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Revised script pages, by Larry Gelbart, 11/28/96, 24p. - Revised pages, 11/30/96, 6p. - Revised pages, 12/2/96, 14p. - Revised pages, 12/7/96, 8p. - Revised pages, 12/13/96, 3p. - Revised pages, 12/28/96, 12p.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised, 10/21/96 - 1/6/97, 131p.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 160, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, memos, clippings, congratulatory cards, 5/97 - 8/97. Approx. 50 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 3)
      Script, no title page, no date, annotated, 111 pages. - Handwritten notes relating to annotations in script, no date, 4 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Script: No title page. Marked "As of 1/7/97." 94 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Marked "#103, chance all Midwest Interbells to Southwest Interbells." Final revision, 11/14/96. Approx. 120p.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Final revision, 11/14/96, some annotations, 108 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Final revision, 11/11/96, marked "not distributed, needs to be proof read," some annotations, 108 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 183, Folder 8)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised 10/21 & 10/28/96, some annotations, 108 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Marked "received 10/7/96." Some annotations. 111 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Marked "Revisions - 10/16/96, 10/17/96, 10/29/96." Also marked "# 8." Heavily annotated. 107 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 3)
      Script. No title page. Dated 10/01/96. 111 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Heavily annotated title page. Marked "received 9/12/96." 128 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. 2 copies: One marked "Harlin." Both are dated September 11, 1996,. Both 128 pages. The Harlin copy is heavily annotated.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 6)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised, July 1, 1996, 128 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 184, Folder 7)
      Script: Blue revision pages only. Dated October 21, 1996. Some annotations.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 185, Folder 1)
      Script revision pages. Dated October-December 1996.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 185, Folder 2)
      Story boards. Marked "Not final: Complete set of scene planned to date." Dated Tuesday, November 5, 1996. 237 scenes.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 185, Folder 3)
      Copy 2 of story boards for November 5, 1996.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 185, Folder 4)
      Story boards revisions dated 10/07/96, 10/15/96, 12/02/96, and two are without dates. 6 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 185, Folder 5)
      Shooting schedules, November 22, 1996. Packets include oneline schedules and crew information. 2 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 1)
      Production materials - Oneline schedules. November - December 1996. 9 packets.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 2)
      Production materials - Staff and crew list. October - November 1996. 5 packets.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 3)
      Production memoranda regarding shooting, special effects and production crew. Dated 11/95 - 4/97.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 4)
      Production materials regarding editing and continuity. No dates. 15 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 5)
      Production memoranda - Regarding casting. Dated July 8 - December 2, 1996. 43 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 6)
      Budget materials, 9 items: Dated October 14 - December 23, 1996.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 7)
      Production materials. - Correspondence regarding legal issues and contract negotiations (August, 1995 - December, 1996).
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 8)
      HBO's Media Moguls, Prepared for Larry Gelbart, by Bobette Buster, August 3, 1995, Los Angeles." Pre-script research packet with clippings on various media personalities. Includes table of contents.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 9)
      Production materials regarding script. - Typographical errata, name changes, and conflicts as reported by DeForest research. Dated May 3 - December 24, 1996. 19 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 186, Folder 10)
      News articles regarding production and some research articles regarding broadcast and print media. June 3 - November 26, 1996. 10 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Script revisions. - MS notes, no date, 20 p. - Outlines and character development sheets (5 pages), no date. - First 42 pages of a script, no date. - Misc. revised script pages, 3/6/97 - 4/7/97.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 2)
      Outlines for scenes. Dated June 6 - June 19, 1996. Some annotations. 8 items.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 3)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. First draft, April 10 1996, 112 p.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 4)
      Screenplay. No title page. Marked "6/25/96." 123 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 5)
      Screenplay. No title page. Marked "6/28/96." Annotated. 126 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 6)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. Revised draft, June 28, 1996, annotated, 124 pages.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 7)
      View preview materials: Dubin Market Research Inc, Summary of Research Findings for March 13th and 27th preview screenings. Includes viewer response forms (32) from the March 13th viewing.
    - WEAPONS OF MASS DISTRACTION (HBO, 1997) (Box 187, Folder 8)
      Notes for advertising copy. Dated November 12, 1996 - March 28, 1997.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW - Pilot (Box 144, Folder 8)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Draft, 11/09/72, 40 p. - First draft, 11/01/72, 42 p. - Draft, no date, 40 p.
    - WIN A FEW, LOSE A FEW - Pilot (Box 151, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. No date, annotated, 40 p.
    - YOUR SHOW OF SHOWS - RIGHT HAND MAN (Box 151, Folder 12)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. First draft, n.d., annotated, 30 p. - Second draft, n.d., 28 p.
    - YOUR SHOW OF SHOWS - PRINCESS FOR A DAY (Box 151, Folder 14)
      Script by Larry Gelbart and Larry Marks. Draft, no date, 15 p.
  - Tributes/Memorials
    - Coleman, Cy (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 1)
      One-page drafts of tribute to Cy Coleman, Sept. 1990, 4 drafts with annotations.
    - Mercer, Johnny (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 2)
      Academy Foundation: "Mercer and the Movies," October 22, 1987. - Scripts for the program (2), one handwritten, no dates. - Program sequences (5) with annotations. - Background materials on Johnny Mercer w/ cover letter from Douglas Edwards 10/24/87.
    - Burns, George (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 3)
      Tribute: "A Gala Evening with George Burns: The Museum of Broadcasting, Sunday, November 5, 1989, The Plaza Hotel, Grand Ballroom." Drafts of Program: Order of Events/Speakers, 4 versions.
    - Buttons, Red (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 4)
      Tribute: Life Time Achievement Award for Red Buttons. Handwritten notepad, 13 pages, undated.
    - Gilford, Jack (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 5)
      Transcript of memorial speech for Jack Gilford given by Larry Gelbart at Minneapolis, 20 June 1990. 3 copies, incl. .1 handwritten.
    - Thomas, Danny (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 6)
      Memorial article written by Larry Gelbart for Danny Thomas. Published in New York Times, February 17, 1991. 2 copies (one is a photocopy). - Two typed originals with cover letters.
    - Berle, Ruth (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 7)
      Eulogy given by Larry Gelbart at Temple Emanu-El, 30 April, 1989, 6 typed versions with annotations.
    - Crosby, Bing (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 8)
      Memorial (to Crosby) and tribute to his partner, Bob Hope. - 3 typed transcripts by Larry Gelbart, March 1, 1982. - One handwritten draft.
    - Penn, Arthur (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 9)
      Tribute given by Larry Gelbart, June 1990. Typed transcript, in the form of a primer, with cover letter and annotations. - MS transcript, also in primer form.
    - Caesar, Sid (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 10)
      Museum of Broadcasting Tribute to Sid Caesar, November 9 - December 31, 1982. - Program with "an appreciation by Steve Allen." - Two articles: Daily News 11/12/82 & Washington Post, n.d.. - Handwritten speech by Larry Gelbart, 4 pages.
    - Berle, Milton (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 11)
      Museum of Broadcasting Tribute to Milton Berle, April 19 - May 30, 1985. Program, 51 p. - 2 typed versions of speech by Larry Gelbart, and 11 handwritten pages, and 6 pages of notes.
    - Hope, Bob (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 12)
      Museum of Broadcasting Tribute, May 2-June 14, 1986, Exhibit" A Half Century on Radio and Television:, 78 p. - Dinner speech, St. Regis Hotel, N.Y.C., 6 pages of notes, notecards 2 -22. - Invitation to Studio2, NBC Burbank: 85th Birthday Celebration.
    - Benny, Jack (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 13)
      Letter and contract with the Museum of Broadcasting re: Jack Benny book and exhibition, incl. it's Statement of Purpose. 7 drafts/versions (typed) of L.G.'s Forward to MB 's book. - Incl. background information on Jack Benny.
    - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 8)
      Washington's Salute to President Kennedy, Jan.1964: texts by L. G. for several participants, ms draft and typed versions. Incl. telegram from Lyndon Johnson and note from The White House. - "JFK Remembered", Visual Arts Project, 1993, 3 typed versions.
    - Johnson, Lyndon B (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 9)
      Washington's Salute to President Johnson, May 26, 1964. Program with Presidential seal and Participant Backstage Pass for Larry Gelbart. Gelbart wrote material for Gregory Peck, Allan Sherman, Gina Lollobrigida.
    - Siegel, Don (Box Ser. C-15, Folder 8)
      "A Memorial Celebration for Don Siegel, October 26, 1912 - April 20, 1991." A pamphlet for a memorial held at the Directors Guild of America, June 8, 1991.
    - Kennedy Center Honors (Box Ser. C-23, Folder 5)
      Booklet from the 1995 Kennedy Center Honors. Awards were given to Jacques d'Amboise, Marilyn Horne, B.B. King, Sidney Poitier, & Neil Simon. Cover is autographed by participants.
    - Lehman, Ernest (Box Ser. C-23, Folder 6)
      Tribute for Ernest Lehman's 80th birthday, written by Larry Gelbart. Includes correspondence with Steven Suskin who coordinated the tribute.
    - Averback, Hy (Box Ser. C-23, Folder 7)
      Tribute to Hy Averback hosted by Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters. Correspondence with Larry Gelbart regarding tribute, May 3 1996.
    - Burns, George (Box Ser. C-23, Folder 8)
      Tribute to George Burns for his 100th Birthday and a dedication of The Burns & Allen Research Institute.
    - Wilder, Billy (Box Ser. C-23, Folder 9)
      Career achievement award, 1995. Presented by the Writers Guild Foundation. Program and rundown.
    - Granoff, Buddy (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 3)
      Memorial: "A Few Words about Buddy." Eulogy given by Larry Gelbart at the Riverside Memorial Chapel in New York City, April 30, 1996. 3 pages. 2 copies. - Similar eulogy given at the Friars Club, Beverly Hills, June 1996.
    - Schwartz, Sherwood (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 4)
      Program and speech for the Sherwood Schwartz dinner at the Beverly Hills Theatre Guild. Schwartz received the Spotlight Award. October 29, 1995.
    - Burton, Jay (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 8)
      Transcript of eulogy given at the Jay Burton Memorial Service, April 28, 1993.
    - Benny, Jack (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 11)
      Foreword by Larry Gelbart for a book about Jack Benny. No date. 2 pages.
    - Weiss, Lou (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 12)
      Transcript of speech given to honor Lou Weiss. 2 pages. No date. Annotated.
    - Greenbaum, Everett & Hal Kantor (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 13)
      Transcript of tribute given to Everett Greenbaum and Hal Kantor, marked "Birthday Party, Winter '92." 4 pages.
    - Mancini, Henry (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 3)
      Tribute speeches for Henry Mancini. Written by Larry Gelbart, delivered by various celebrities. Speeches dated 4/18/94. - Contact speech for possible participants.
    - Simon, Neil (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 4)
      New York Friars Club Tribute to Neil Simon, April 25 1993. Program and seating. - Excerpt from "Art of Theater." Souvenir booklet. - Letters to Larry Gelbart re: speech given at the tribute.
    - Reiner, Carl and Estelle (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 12)
      Transcript of speech given at the Reiner's 50th Anniversary celebration, December 3, 1993.
    - Kantor, Joseph S (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 13)
      Transcript of eulogy given at the Memorial Service for Joseph S. Kantor, April 26, 1993.
    - Julian, Arthur (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 14)
      Transcript of eulogy given at the Arthur Julian Memorial Service, Writers Guild of America Theater, March 3, 1995.
    - Edwards, Blake (Box Ser. C-30, Folder 4)
      Preston Sturges Award presented to Blake Edwards by the Writers Guild of America, west amd the Directors Guild of America. October 22-4, 1993.
    - Sondheim, Stephen (Box Ser. C-30, Folder 6)
      Q/A session with Stephen Sondheim, no date.
    - Lewis, Catherine (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 3)
      Draft letter of condolence "Dear Hannah and David, no date. - Another condolence leter " Dear Felicia" re Nick.no date.
    - Fuchs, Michael (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 10)
      Two souvenier booklets from the People for Americam Way's 1996 "Spirit of Liberty Award dinner honoring Michael Fuchs.
    - Averback, Hy (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 15)
      Transcript of speech given in tribute by Larry Gelbart at the Pacifc Pioneer Broadcaster Luncheon. No date.
    - Arnold, Danny (Box Ser. C-34, Folder 34)
      Invitation to a surprise birthday party/tribute. Invitation is in the form of a Daily Racing Form. January 27, 1990.
    - Caesar, Sid (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 3)
      Articles honoring Sid Caesar and "Caesar's Hour," 1996.
    - Hope, Bob (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 8)
      Articles of tribute to the career of Bob Hope, 1996. - Correspondence with the Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, re: "Bob Hope and the Academy: 50-50," May 20, 1996.
    - Paar, Jack (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 23)
      Handwritten notes on cards, 9 cards, no date.
    - JOEL GREY - FAREWELL APPEARANCE (Box 150, Folder 4)
      Annotated monologue, no date, 4 p. - Another typed draft of monologue, n.d., 3p. - Handwritten draft, incomplete. n.d., 2p.
- Publications
  - Ecstasy Business (The) by Richard Condon, c. 1967 (Box 301, Folder 10)
    With note: Working copy May 28, 1968.
  - Golden Kazoo (The) by John G. Schneider, c. 1956 (Box 302, Folder 1)
- Speeches
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 6)
    Population Institute Speech written by Larry Gelbart for Jack Lemmon. Three copies. No date. 2 pages.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 7)
    Invitation to Speak at the Annual Supreme Court Luncheon, June 7, 1983. - Letter from Louis C. Blau, attached article by Gelbart: "In Defense of Laughter. - Typed transcript of Gelbart speech, annotated, 14 p. - Handwritten speech, 15 p.
  - Dukakis, Michael (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 10)
    Campaign speeches for Governor Dukakis, written by Larry Gelbart, 1988: MS draft for speech on George Bush, 6 p., Terrorism (3 p), GOP Primer (2 p), Declaration of candidacy, (2 speeches, 5 p. & 8 p.)
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-5, Folder 2)
    Foundation for New American Music, 9/14/80 & 1982. ABC: "State of TV," 9/15/77. - Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters Lunch, 5/15/87, photos (6) Gelbart, C. Reiner, G. Reynolds, etc. - Academy Awards, 11/12/81 - Laurel Awards (P. Chayefski).
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-5, Folder 3)
    University of Southern California, Marked "1973 or 1974?," typed copy and 2 sets of notes. - Commencement Speech for Cinema-Television, 5/9/91. - Printed reproductions of Commencement speech (Emmy, Washington Post)
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-5, Folder 4)
    Speech for Sandra Moss, Chairperson of SHARE. May, 1988. - 2 Thank you letters from Moss to Gelbart.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 10)
    Misc speeches, one dated January 2, 1991. 8 items.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 1)
    Speech for Doctor's Luncheon in Chicago. Given at Cedars-Sinai.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 7)
    "The Jewish Artist: Realities and Myths." Transcript of Speech given to the Hadassah Beverly Hills Chapter, April 20 1994. Includes cover letter as invitation, January 10, 1994.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 17)
    Transcript of speech given at the Palm Springs Museum to the Women's Committee. January 23, 1995.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 1)
    Humanatias Prize Luncheon, Keynote Address. Given by Larry Gelbart at the Sheraton Universal Hotel, July 6, 1995. - Transcript, 9 pages, letters of thanks re: speech. - Program and list of prize finalists.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 21)
    The Internation Friends of Grafitti Appreciation and Recital Society." Humorous speech written by Larry Gelbart and Jerry Ross, no date.
  - Dukakis, Michael (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 37)
    Photocopy of a handwritten speech for Michael Dukakis. Marked: "Attn: Marty Kaplan." Ends with "Larry Gelbart, Capri, Italy, 24 August, 1988." 5 pages.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 6)
    Humanitas Prize Luncheon, Keynote address by Larry Gelbart. July 6, 1995. 9 pages.
  - Speeches (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 25)
    Text of speech delivered at the Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters Lunch, May 15, 1987, 11 pages.
- Subject Files
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 14)
    Museum of Broadcasting Newsletters: vol. 7, no. 3 (Sid Caesar), vol. 10, no. 1, 1986 (Larry Gelbart seminars at the museum), vol. 10, no. 2, 1986, Milton Berle.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 15)
    Fifth Annual Television Festival - Order of Presentation for opening event, March 7, 1988. - 6 drafts of texts for Julie Andrews and Larry Gelbart. Incl. brochures and programs.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-1, Folder 16)
    Council of Producers, Directors, Writers, Journalists, and Performers for the Museum of Broadcasting. Membership list, February 18, 1987. 5 pages.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 1)
    2nd Annual Los Angeles Festival. Two Newsprint brochures for the Television Festival in Los Angeles, May 10-26, 1985.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 2)
    3rd Annual Los Angeles Festival. Newsprint brochure, March 1986.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 3)
    Publicity Packet of Exhibits. Topics include: BBC External Services, HBO: Reflections from a Decade, A Personal View by Alistair Cooke, MB News, Hanna Barbera: 25 Years, Muppets, Bob and Ray: A Retrospective, See It Now, Toscanini, Master Theatre.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 4)
    Programs for Seminars on Writing for TV. - Interview with Larry Gelbart, 70 p. - Transcripts of Seminars, October 2-5, 1984, 139 p. - Flyer/Schedule. - Biography with Credits, 6 pages. - Seminar notes.
  - Museum of Broadcasting (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re: Television Series, Tributes, Seminars, Exhibits, New Museum Building, Television Festival.
  - Congressional Hearings (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 13)
    "Sex and Violence on TV." Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Communications of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce: House of Representatives: 94th Congress: July 9, August 17-18, 1976: Serial No. 94-140. Annotated Transcript, 378 p.
  - National Constitution Center (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 1)
    Correspondence and minutes from board meetings. Larry Gelbart was a member of the Board of Directors. July 20, 1988 - June 25, 1991. 42 items. - Illustrate & Learn, study packet for elementary aged children re: amendments, 1991. - Report on Audits.
  - Beverly Hills Police Department (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 10)
    Text for public service announcements (television). Version A and Version B, 1 page each. Written by Larry Gelbart. Starring [Burt?] Reynolds. No date.
  - You Should See What You're Missing (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 11)
    Chicago Public Television Forum style broadcast, April 20, 1976, WTTW/ Channel 11. Articles (4) relating to broadcast, in which Larry Gelbart was a participant.
  - Weston, Jay (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 15)
    Jay Weston's Restaurant Review. Issue #20, 1988. See "From Russia with Love," p. 8. Describes culinary tour of Russia with Larry Gelbart.
  - Alvord Stag (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 15)
    Short stories about Alvord Stag by Larry Gelbart. - First copy, 4 pages, no date. -Second copy, in four chapters, annotated, 19 p, no date.
  - Broadway Cares & Equity Fights AIDS (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 16)
    Letter from Sandy Schreiber re: Gelbart's contribution to "Broadway: Day & Night," January 15, 1991. - Gelbart's article (4 drafts).
  - Equinox Films (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 17)
    4 pages of typed notes marked "1989, Notes for Equinox Films' 'The Human Language'-- a documentary still in process of being assempled."
  - University of Southern California (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 18)
    Correspondence 1991 (School of Cinema-Television).
  - Resumes (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 19)